ocreef.com 2011-02-25

# Secure Online Aquarium Supply Store

We'll Protect Your Privacy 100%

**Privacy Policy & Security:**  
At OCReef.com, we are 100% committed to electronic security. We value our customers, and want to build and maintain your trust by doing everything possible to ensure the most secure and private environment in which to shop. The following information describes our Privacy Policy in regard to the personal information you provide us; along with information we obtain about how our visitors use our site. ****  
Back to Top

**Personal Information:**  
Upon placing your first order on OCReef.com, you will be asked to provide billing and shipping information that will be stored securely and used to process your order. Your information will then be pre-filled for your convenience on future orders. We can also pre-fill your credit card information on subsequent orders if you choose this option. Information you supply is protected by your personal Password, along with your User ID, so that only you have access to your account information. By clicking on the Login link at the top of each page, you are free to review or change your account information at any time.  
Back to Top

**E-mail:**  
You have our assurance that we do not rent or sell your e-mail address to anyone. We use your email address to send order-related emails only, like shipping confirmations. We will contact you if we have a question about an order you placed. If we are unable to reach you by phone, we may also try to contact you by e-mail.  
Back to Top

**Ironclad Secure Shopping:**  
As a Google, PayPal, and LinkPoint Certified Merchant, we have agreed to abide by the principles outlined in their Privacy Policies. All orders placed on our store site are encrypted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology - rated one of the most prevalent and secure systems available for online store customers. SSL is an extremely complex form of cryptography that makes it virtually impossible for a third party to decrypt any personal information you provide. You can shop in confidence and be assured that your personal and credit card information is protected when transmitted online. To learn more about SSL technology and how it works you can go online and use any of the major search engines. A great place to start is by visiting [Webopedia's discussion on SSL](http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/S/SSL.html "Webopedia's Discussion on SSL"). [](https://www.ocreef.com/comodo_ssl_credentials_ocreef "Comodo Secured Authentic Website")

**JavaScript:**  
OCReef.com incorporates JavaScript throughout our site for many useful features such as instantly displaying backordered items, recalculating your order total upon selecting a different shipping method, and for displaying pop-up information for products and assistance. These features are designed to enhance your online shopping experience and to make shopping online more convenient for our customers. However, having JavaScript enabled, isn't a requirement for using our site. We do recommend using Adobe Flash Player, a cross-platform browser plug-in that delivers breakthrough Web experiences to over 98% of Internet users. See the following link to obtain the latest version of   
[Adobe's Flash Player](http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/ "Adobe Flash Player").  
Back to Top

**Links to Other Sites:** ****  
This site may contain links to other sites. The privacy policies of these sites may differ from those of OCReef.com. Make sure you are educated on any site's policies before providing personal information.  
Back to Top

**Choice/Opt-Out:**   
When registering with OCReef.com, we will ask for contact information, such as your name and email address. We will use the customer contact information from the registration form to send you information about our company and some of our partners. OCReef.com sends subscribed users regular newsletters and occasional promotional offers. However, OCReef.com provides users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. If you do not wish to receive correspondence from OCReef.com, use the easy unsubscribe option.  
Back to Top

**Updating or Correcting Your Information:**   
If you need to change or correct any information you provided OCReef.com, you can make edits by logging in to "My Account."  
Back to Top

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy:**   
When new policies are put into practice, notices of changes will appear on this page in advance, so check back often.  
Back to Top

« Back to Homepage
